Jake Hui Wang

A full-stack web developer with experience building apps and developing websites in JavaScript, React, and Ruby on Rails. I want to utilize my passion to learn and work with the latest technologies to grow as a developer while helping companies advance in the software engineering industry. I also bring strong problem-solving skills that will further a company's effectiveness and efficiency of organizational success.

PROJECTS

NPM simple-react-google-maps — Github | Link

Google Maps React.js Component

- Developed an open-source NPM package for React.js applications
- Allow developers to quickly and simply render Google Maps in their projects

Parallel — Github | Link

An Airbnb for parking cars full stack web application

- Designed and coded the app's front-end with React, Redux, HTML, and CSS
- Built the back-end with Ruby on Rails and utilize PostgreSQL as database
- Implemented an authentication and authorization system with JWT tokens

EXPERIENCE

Digidems, Virginia Beach, Virginia — Campaign Tech Specialist

June 2018 - Dec 2018

- Designed and developed software programs for voter outreach and financial reporting.
- Provided cybersecurity training and integrated best practices into the workflow to minimize the risk of hacking.
- Utilized computer programming, new technologies, and modern software to maximize campaign efficiency.

Heart To Heart Home Care, Brooklyn, New York — Data Specialist

Jan 2015 - June 2017

- Increased productivity by creating Microsoft Excel programs to eliminate repetitive tasks.
- Analyzed data and accurately created reports to evaluate the company's performance.
- Processed payroll for thousands of employees and billed multi-million dollars in claims weekly.

J&JC Beer Distribution, Elmhurst, New York — Data Specialist

Sep 2012 - Jan 2015

- Processed orders, created invoices, and maintained daily records of sales.
- Supervised inventory control, coordinated deliveries, and communicated with suppliers.
- Supported the sales team with pricing and calculated commission for each sales representative.

Personal Info

Queens, New York (646) 206-5709 huiwang339@gmail.com

Links

jakeww.com Github LinkedIn

SKILLS

Javascript
Python
React
Redux
Node.js
Ruby
Ruby On Rails
SQL
PostgreSQL
HTML
CSS

Education

Flatiron School New York, NY Nov 2017 Full Stack Web Development

Stony Brook
University
Stony Brook, NY
May 2012
Bachelor of Science
in Health Science